# Mustapha Deen

7525 Mcwhorter Place, Annandale VA

**Phone:** (571)-226-7974 | **Email:** mdeen3@outlook.com

Talented, enthusiastic and technically strong individual with over 2 years of front-end web development and technical experience. I have real passion for coding technology and software and possess proven ability of balancing multiple work streams within a fast paced, demanding environment. With excellent HTML, CSS (SASS), JavaScript and Vue.js development skills, currently I'm seeking to continue my career with a vibrant company that will allow me to be part of a highly collaborative team, develop my technical skills and work on projects for challenging client requirements.

### **#Skills**

Front-End Source Control Frameworks UI/UX Other

JavaScript ES6 / jQuery CSS / SASS / HTML / XHTML / Gulp / Web pack

508 Accessibility

**Terminal** 

GitHub Jira / Bitbucket

Git (Git Flow)

React / Redux Bootstrap Wireframing / UML Prototyping Adobe Suite

Atomic Design

Microsoft Office Skype Business

# **#Professional Experience**

### Hilton Hotel / Front Desk Agent

December 2018 - Current: Mclean, VA

LMake reservations or appointments for guests who want to avail themselves of local entertainment or services

Ly Answer guest calls and record details of each conversation for future follow-up

Li Meet and exceed guests' expectations by anticipating the services they might require and suggesting local venues

LCommunicate with the booking, housekeeping and maintenance departments to ensure prompt responses to guests' needs

#### The Swiss Bakery / Webmaster/Marketing

October 2017 – June 2018: Springfield, VA | Remote

L, Coordinate ongoing production of Swiss Bakery digital platform, creating and updating web pages in HTML, CSS and some JavaScript, and serve as first responder to digital-platform bugs/outages/performance issues

LWorking with marketing and design entities, marketing using Constant Contact

LyWork on various digital-platform enhancement efforts, such as web page redesigns, search engine optimization, widget integration, and other evolving initiatives

Ly Inventory control, packing and sending out mail orders and receiving of shipments.

#### Northern Virginia Community College / Computer Lab Technician

December 2016 - August 2017: Annandale, VA |

LSupporting computer labs and aiding people technical difficulties

LResolving IT related problems with computers and associated peripherals working in an IT department.

LaProviding one-on-one or group tutoring in a higher education environment.

LSupporting instructional technology that may be found in a

LWorking with the Microsoft Suite of applications

## #Education

George Mason University / Bachelor in Computer Science

September 2018 - September 2020: Fairfax, VA

FreeCodeCamp / Certificate in Responsive Web design